export const pythonLoopsAssignment = {
  title: 'Python Loops â€“ Assignment',
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Which loop is preferred when number of iterations is fixed?',
      options: ['while', 'for', 'nested', 'pass'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Which loop checks condition before execution?',
      options: ['do-while', 'repeat', 'while', 'for'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'What happens if while condition is always true?',
      options: [
        'Loop runs once',
        'Loop stops',
        'Infinite loop',
        'Syntax error',
      ],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Which loop is best for iterating a list?',
      options: ['while', 'for', 'if', 'pass'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'range(0,10,2) gives?',
      options: [
        '0 1 2 3 4',
        '0 2 4 6 8',
        '1 3 5 7 9',
        'Error',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Which is NOT a loop?',
      options: ['for', 'while', 'if', 'nested'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Nested loop means?',
      options: [
        'Loop with break',
        'Loop inside another loop',
        'Infinite loop',
        'Conditional loop',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Which keyword controls repetition?',
      options: ['def', 'loop', 'for', 'return'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Loops are commonly used with?',
      options: ['Lists', 'Strings', 'Ranges', 'All'],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Loops are fundamental to?',
      options: [
        'Logic building',
        'Automation',
        'Problem solving',
        'All',
      ],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
  ],
}